# JERRY JACKSON

123 Main Street, Tampa, Florida, 33609 j.jackson@youremail.com (123) 456-7890 Technically skilled and highly professional secretary with a business administration degree from the Florida Institute of Technology. Exceptional computer skills, including MS Office, Outlook Mail, CRM systems, and client booking systems. Aptitude for customer service, communication in-person and over the phone, problem-solving, and administration. Also has 2 years of industry secretarial experience, including working for two well-established accountancy firms. Dedicated to business success and improving working efficiency.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### SECRETARY

Pitcher and Company Tampa CPA Firm, Tampa, FL | January 2020 - February 2021

- Responsible for filing and scanning client's legal documents
- Scheduled client travel arrangements, meetings, and interviews
- Managed and updated all calendars and diaries for managerial staff
- Answered incoming emails and telephone calls
- Organized and filed all office paperwork and documents

#### SECRETARY

Walter S Sanders & Associates, Tampa, FL | July 2018 - January 2020

- Implement effective company policies to ensure that all practices comply with labor and employment regulations
- Increased employee retention rates by managing workplace satisfaction to an over 90% success rate by creating and maintaining a positive work environment
- Develop targeted outreach practices to increase minority recruitment and ensure compliance with affirmative action policies
- Monitor scheduled in and out times as well as employee breaks to ensure that proper employment laws are met

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

Florida Institute Of Technology Melbourne, Fl | August 2015 - July 2018

## **KEY SKILLS**

- IT proficiency, including Microsoft Office (data sorting, validation, and filters)
- Knowledge of CRM and client booking systems
- Office management
- Administration
- Diary management
- Knowledge of CRM and client booking systems
- Excellent communication skills

## CERTIFICATIONS

 Certified Administrative Professional by The International Association of Administrative Professionals, July 2018